(Leonard:)Feel like trying something new
for dinner?
Maybe Indian? Tex-Mex?
(Sheldon:)Ever wonder how humans would
be different if they evolved...
(Sheldon:)...from lizards instead of mammals?
(Leonard:)Okay, let's talk about that.
(Sheldon:)As you know,
lizards, cold-blooded animals...
(Sheldon:)...lack the ability to sense temperature.
(Sheldon:)But they do move more sluggishly
when it's cold.
(Sheldon:)So lizard weathermen
would say things like:
"Bring a sweater, it's slow outside."
(Sheldon:)I love my mind.
(Leonard:)We all do. Now, how about dinner?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I would assume we'd enjoy insects
or smaller lizards.
(Sheldon:)We could also pull each other's tails off
and grill them. They'll just grow back.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Sheldon:)My life-size cardboard
Mr. Spock is here.
(Sheldon:)I know he wouldn't care
for an outburst of human emotion...
(Sheldon:)...but, oh, goodie, oh, goodie,
oh, goodie.